Hey everyone, I wanted to
make this quick video for you
to show you how
Tiquiz works. This is a
somewhat temporary video
because right now, we're
in the beta phase,
which means all the
people joining Tiquiz
today can request
features, ask for
improvements, that kind of thing.
That's why I'm making a
slightly quick video,
just to show you the
rough idea of how it works.
When you've placed an order for
your Tiquiz access,
you'll get an email
with a login link.
Very simple, you click
to log in and you
land directly in
your Tiquiz dashboard.
You'll see, I kept things
as simple as possible.
This is a brand-new
account.
Here you've got a little guided
tour to teach you
how to use the tool,
although it's still
fairly easy.
I'll let you discover it
once you're inside.
What I wanted to show you
is this section here,
"settings," which lets you
pick the
interface language.
Tiquiz is fully
multilingual, meaning
you can switch it to
English, you can
set it to any
language you want.
If that bugs you,
bam, just turn it off.
We're going
to switch back to French.
Here, you can choose
whether you address your
audience casually or formally.
And here, you can
describe your target audience.
Let's say we're
working for a
small side business I run.
Here, you can
enter your privacy
policy,
which will let you
have it
directly in your quizzes
afterward, without having
to re-enter it.
So we'll drop it in here.
There.
Done.
We can save it.
Next, we're heading into
branding, which lets you
have your
logo on your quiz directly, and
have it built
with the right colors, the
right font, the direct link
to your website.
And here, you'll get to
pick your tone of voice.
This is the only slightly
technical part, and even then, you'll
see it's very simple.
Plus, I explained
everything clearly.
This is the part that connects
Tiquiz to Systeme.io.
Here, we'll put "Test."
Very simply,
what you're going to do
is head over to
your Systeme.io account.
I created one here
for this demo.
You're going to go into your
settings, and once in your
settings, you'll go into
MCP Key and API, and you'll
simply create a
new key, which we'll call,
say, Tiquiz. We
don't give it an expiration date
since we want it
to work all the time.
We save.
There we go.
Here, we copy the token, and
we paste it over here,
that's it.
Don't worry,
everything is encrypted.
On my end, I never
see your information,
everything is secure.
Once we're here,
you'll see
it's very simple.
Basically, Tiquiz
is going to take the people who
answer your quiz and
leave their email, and it'll
send them into your
Systeme.io account with a tag.
From there, that's where
you can trigger
whatever you want.
Meaning Tiquiz lets you
generate
results based on
your visitor's profile,
and each result
can have its own tag.
So let's say you
have a quiz for skill levels —
beginner,
intermediate, expert.
You'll be able to
create on your
Systeme.io account a tag
"beginner," "advanced," "expert."
And so each person
can then receive
exactly what they asked for.
For example, we're going to
our CRM, we're going to
pick "tag" and we'll create
a tag, for example, quiz-beginner.
Then,
we're simply going to
create our quiz.
Here you have three
ways to create a quiz.
You can build it
manually, filling in the
quiz title, the intro
text, and you can
build everything manually.
That's for folks
who really want full
control over every detail.
What we're interested in
today for this
video is to
create a quiz with AI.
And you also have — sorry,
I forgot to mention, you
can import a file,
meaning import a quiz
built somewhere else.
If you have no idea what
quiz to do, you can brainstorm
with Tiquiz so it gives
you quiz ideas.
Here, we're not going to do that,
but I'll let you
discover it once
you're inside.
We're going to choose the
goals of our quiz.
For example, we're
going to say that
we want to educate and guide.
You don't have to pick
more than one,
you can pick just one.
We're going to make a short quiz.
The target audience is already
pre-filled, but you can
narrow it down if you want.
And we'll do a quiz by
skill level. We'll ask for the first name
and we'll ask for gender, and
we'll say we're building this quiz
to send the right resource
to the visitor based on their
skill level on
treatment.
Here, we'll say we have a
lead magnet to offer,
which is a guide
for patients on GLP-1.
And we want a quiz
in French, but
you can pick multiple
languages if you want.
We're going to ask Tiquiz
to generate the quiz for us.
What you don't see happening
behind the scenes is that
we have a full
prompt system that builds a
quiz optimized
to go viral, to be
interesting to visit and
answered by your visitors,
which will actually attract
people who are qualified
for your offers.
Because right off the bat, if they
fill out the quiz, it means
your topic interests them.
If your topic didn't
interest them,
they wouldn't even
start your quiz.
For example, if you see
a quiz about DIY
and you don't like
DIY, you don't
do DIY,
you're not going to take the quiz.
On the other hand, if it's your
field, you'll be
interested, and right away, you'll
be a hot prospect for
the person who created the quiz.
Here, you can see that was
super fast.
We've got a quiz that's been
created. So here, you'll
find the intro.
Also, here, everything is editable,
you can change everything.
For example,
if you want the text
left-aligned,
you just click on it.
You can add
text however you want.
You can change
the button labels.
For example,
we'll put "Take the quiz."
I need to fix that.
You see, that's why
we're in the beta phase,
because these kinds of small
details still need
a bit of polishing.
It built four questions for us,
and we can see that each
time, it assigns
points toward the results.
The results,
we're going to go see them.
They're here.
So here,
we're going to grab the first name of the
person, since they
filled it in at the beginning.
And this is one result.
So, one of the results
that'll be shown to
visitors of your quiz.
You can change everything at
every level to
add information, and
each time you can
add a call to action
that's different depending on
the result and where you
want to send the
person.
Knowing that here,
you'll have the tags.
There.
Here, we find our tag
quiz-beginner that we created
earlier, which you
can assign based on
the result.
Now, these results —
how are they calculated?
Very simply, with
a points system.
You'll assign points,
for each answer,
on each question.
It's hard to get
simpler, knowing that
Tiquiz
has set it all up for you anyway.
The important step next
is the information capture.
So this is where you'll
ask the person to
enter their name and email.
You can ask
for just the email, but if
you go into the settings,
you'll see you can
also ask for the first name.
I personally like having
the first name to
really personalize my
communication afterward.
Here,
we said we'd ask for
gender and first name.
We're going to request a share.
That's
optional, you're not
required to ask for it.
For example, if
you make quizzes on
slightly 🍑 🍆 topics,
maybe you don't want to
force your
visitors to share the quiz.
Here, you can do it, and you
can offer them an extra bonus
if they share
your quiz. The point is
to boost the virality
of your quiz, because then
every person who takes the
quiz will be invited to
share it.
They can also skip
this step and go
straight to their results.
But either way, each one
can share it if they
want to, every time.
And that's great
for bringing you
organic traffic.
Imagine you have ten
people who share with ten
people, and those ten
people share with another ten
people — obviously your
quiz is going to reach a
phenomenal scale without
spending a dime on ads.
And for that, it's good to
offer them a little bonus,
a little —
depending on your field.
A PDF, a video,
a training, whatever.
You can add a visual
for your bonus, and
you can customize the
message that comes with
your share.
Here, you can assign
another tag for
people who shared your
quiz, so you can also automate
the bonus delivery.
Here, you'll get to pick
the design of your quiz.
So you'll be able to
pick the font.
Right now,
there aren't many.
If you want more,
just ask me.
You can pick the
main color.
For example, if you're more
into turquoise or green
and you want a
background color, for example, a
slightly blue one, that's totally
doable, and you can
add your logo, which will show
up at the end of your
quiz.
Let's drop this
logo in randomly.
In the top right, you can
preview your quiz in mobile
format, since of course it's
optimized for mobile display
too, so you can
be sure your
visitors, even if they're not
on a PC, can clearly
see your quiz.
Once that's done, you'll
be able to publish your
quiz to mark it as
active, which also lets you
unpublish it when
you no longer want it
active.
And here, we'll be able
to share it.
Um, here you can
customize your URL.
So, for example, we'll put
the name of the thing
I'm promoting for this test.
Once we've done all that,
we're going to go see what
our quiz looks like.
So just click on
the little icon
here to copy the link.
That's the link you'll
share directly with your
visitors on your socials, etc.
And we'll be able to see
the quiz we just built.
So here we find the
logo, which will be yours.
Same at the bottom.
We find "This quiz is
offered by my brand," and
the quiz intro.
So let's take it.
This is optional, you
don't have to enable it,
but it was requested,
so I added it.
OK, we're going to take the quiz
quickly because we
don't care about the results
for this video.
We enter the email,
we accept the privacy
policy, that way
we're compliant with GDPR.
That's your privacy
policy showing up,
the one we saw at the start
of this video, the one you
enter in your settings.
Because I don't store,
I don't use your,
your emails are encrypted on
my side, I don't see them.
So you're the one
managing these emails.
We'll request to access
the results, and that's where
we'll get offered
the viral share.
Here, I'm offered to
share on the social
networks I picked
to unlock an
extra bonus.
Let's say I'm going to
copy to Facebook.
There, as if I wanted to
share, boom, the quiz.
We're doing this roughly,
no big deal, it's just so
you get the idea. I
come back here, it tells me my
my bonus has been unlocked.
I don't know if you noticed
just before,
we had a little note
underneath to skip the
share and request access to the
results without sharing.
Here, I'm going to ask to
see my results.
So this is what the AI
generated for us, and you
can customize everything
everywhere. And it confirms
my bonus has been unlocked.
Here, I haven't entered the URL
for my call to action to
then redirect my prospect
to my blog, say,
or my social media.
That's why it
doesn't appear, but
normally, it shows up
just like it should.
Next, if I go back to
Tiquiz and check
the results, we'll see...
I need to refresh.
In my quiz results,
we can see I captured
two leads because I
did it twice
for the sake of the video.
Each time, it shows me
the result breakdown.
It tells me exactly
which answers were
submitted on the quiz, and it tells me
which emails
were captured.
Now, we're going to check
if my contact properly
landed in Systeme.io.
I'm going to refresh.
And you can see that,
my contact arrived
with the matching tag.
What happens once
I land in Systeme.io
with this tag? That's what you
have to set up beforehand.
Let's say you want to
send an email after
the quiz response,
you'll head into
"Automation," then "Workflow."
You'll create a workflow
that we'll call Quiz.
Done.
And you'll open it.
The trigger is very
simple — it's a tag added,
since that's what
Tiquiz does, it imports
the contact with the tag.
The tag, we pick it,
it's this one.
That's what's going to
trigger the automation.
And then,
we're going to add an action.
As an action, you can
do whatever you want.
You can remove another
tag, grant access to a
course, remove access to a
course, enroll in an
email campaign if you want to
send multiple emails.
Anyway, we'll put
"Send an email."
We'll create a new one
to show you
how it works.
It's very simple.
We create our email,
we save.
I don't have a sender
email address because
I just created
this account for the test.
Anyway, you get the idea.
Then, we exit the workflow and
we remember to activate it.
Now, what's going to happen,
if I had a compliant account,
obviously, is that
your visitor who took
the quiz is going to get their
results page, etc.
And in parallel, they'll land
in your Systeme.io account,
they'll get the tag assigned
to them, and behind that,
the workflows you
created will run.
So basically, you have a
visitor you don't
know, you get them
to take the quiz because
it's a topic that
interests them.
You show how much of
an expert you are in your field
because the questions you
ask are spot-on.
They leave their email because
they want to know
more, and they
want to see their results.
They spent two,
three minutes on the quiz,
they want to know what
it gives them as a result.
And once they've left their
email, they just entered
your pool of potential customers.
And that is ultra powerful
because, as a result,
afterward, you'll
be able to send them
emails, you'll be able to
send them lead
magnets, you'll be able to
send them courses.
It's a warm contact,
who's interested in
your field and that you'll
be able to leverage
often for
many, many years.
That's how Tiquiz works.
I hope that was
clear for you.
After this, the rest
is really simple.
Honestly, you're not
going to get lost in it.
You'll find your quizzes here.
For example,
you can delete them.
You can just
edit them.
You can deactivate them.
What are you going to
find here? You'll
find your leads,
all the people you've
captured.
For example, if you're
not using Systeme.io,
you can just
export them as CSV.
What happens is you
get them straight to your
PC in Excel format, basically,
and from there, you'll
be able to import them
directly into your
autoresponder.
You don't even need,
most of the time,
to open the CSV.
You import it directly
into your autoresponder,
it'll be imported with the tag.
You can clearly see this lead
has been synced with
Systeme.io, we can see the date.
Anyway, everything
that matters to us.
Still, I recommend
using Systeme.io
because you can see
it's optimized for Tiquiz.
It's really been optimized
to work with Systeme.io
because it's my tool
and it's the tool that most
people who
get Tiquiz are using.
Down the line,
will I add other
autoresponders? Honestly,
it's not planned.
Again, we're in
the beta phase, with 50
people coming in.
If out of those 50, I
get 10 asking
to add Aweber or
ClickFunnels or any
other autoresponder, we'll
all ask the question
together and see if it
serves several
people, I'll do it. Coming
back to Tiquiz, we'll also
have the stats here, where
you'll be able to track
a bit of everything happening
on your quiz, on your quizzes.
And there you go, we've done the tour.
You have a little
help section that answers
most of your questions.
Same thing,
it's under construction.
You'll have much more
support as we
go along, because
right now, I don't
really know what questions
you'll have, but as
we go, we'll add
more.
And there we go,
I think we've seen it all.
The only tab we haven't seen
is here, "Account & Pricing."
Here, you find your
subscription level, but
since you're
buying during this beta
period, well, at least,
I hope for your sake, when
you watch this video, the
beta isn't over yet,
you'll get a lifetime
access either way, no subscription.
For people who come
after and go on a
subscription, they'll
simply be able to cancel,
upgrade, or downgrade
their subscription from here.
They won't even need
to go into Systeme.io.
Here, you can also
change your password
and delete your account
if you no longer want
your account.
OK, we've done the full tour.
I hope this video
wasn't too long.
I'm truly super, super,
super happy to offer you
this software today
that I coded myself with
my own two hands and with AI.
You can see it already works
really well at 95%.
Now, I need 50
beta testers to
point out the improvements,
the little things I
haven't spotted yet because
I'm all alone
on this, and so I can't
catch everything.
And once that's done,
once those 50 people
have given me their feedback,
we'll move straight
to subscriptions.
Until then, I wish you
a great discovery of Tiquiz.
I really hope I can
bring you into the beta.
You'll find us on the
beta users Telegram group.
You'll see the
vibe is really great.
We're among friends,
we keep it chill, and everyone
gives me their feedback.
I try to answer everyone
as fast as I can.
The vibe is great.
Join us!